[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The smallest monkey on earth is found in the Philippines.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what country did the Kamikaze cocktail reportedly originate?", "correct_answer": "Japan", "incorrect_answers": ["Jamaica", "India", "South Africa"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The famous Statue of Liberty lies between New York and New Jersey.  Another, much smaller Statue of Liberty of the same shape is located where?", "correct_answer": "Paris", "incorrect_answers": ["England", "Canada", "Union of South Africa"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The feathers of adult male ostriches are primarily of this color.", "correct_answer": "Black", "incorrect_answers": ["White", "Gray", "Brown"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who directed, wrote and starred as the newly-elected President of the United States in the 2003 comedy movie Head of State?", "correct_answer": "Chris Rock", "incorrect_answers": ["Martin Lawrence", "Chris Tucker", "Eddie Murphy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what ocean can the 50 species of Exocoetidae, also known as flying fish, be found?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Atlantic ocean", "Indian ocean", "Pacific ocean"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why was the name Mercedes added to Benz?", "correct_answer": "To make it more appealing to the French", "incorrect_answers": ["No one knows", "To make it more feminine", "To make it compete with Ford"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who voiced Roger Rabbit in the 1988 movie Who Framed Roger Rabbit?", "correct_answer": "Charles Fleischer", "incorrect_answers": ["Bob Hoskins", "Mae Questel", "Mel Blanc"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Eddie Slovik was a soldier killed during World War II. How did he die?", "correct_answer": "He was shot by the US for desertion.", "incorrect_answers": ["He was the last US soldier to die in World War II.", "He was the first soldier killed on D-Day.", "He was the only American prisoner of war in Hiroshima when the A-bomb fell."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the best friend and roommate of Julia Roberts character in the film Pretty Woman?", "correct_answer": "Kit", "incorrect_answers": ["Kat", "Lee", "Lou"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What continent are tigers native to?", "correct_answer": "Asia", "incorrect_answers": ["South America", "Africa", "Europe"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Viola plants, commonly referred to as violets, pansies or heartsease, are used as food and in medicine because they are rich in these nutrients.", "correct_answer": "Vitamins A and C", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "Iron and magnesium", "Lycopene and tannin"]}]